Hello hello everyone today our comparison
is about Care Health Insurance
product which was earlier
known as Rally. Subscribe about it
first let's discuss some of the company's details
that it is an Indian health insurance company
which was established in 2012 it is a
standalone health insurance company which has launched
only Wealth in Products in a Quarter
HDFC Ergo
is a general insurance company in Gurgaon which was established in
2012 among the top companies in the market and
their joint venture with Bank Insurance
Company was recently added they
took over Apollo Clinic and this
Optima Restore Plan is a product
in Mumbai let's
start the comparison of the plan if we
talk about sum insured range then
in HDFC Ergo it is from 5 lakh to 50 lakh whereas
in China it is from 3 lakh to 75 lakh
subscribe and
in subscribe your subscriber pays the
doctor's fee before getting admitted in the hospital
from which he charges any
kind of test done  There are small expenses,
subscribe to this and subscribe to
treatment,
which means that for the treatment of any such disease,
you do not need 24-hour
hospitalization,
it is called disease, which is the
appointment and rally of Asirgarh, Discover Road Ambulance
subscription in 2014, if you have done such Tilak and then
hospitalization at ₹15, if the cost is between 5 lakhs to
10 lakhs, then you
can subscribe and subscribe,
Ambulance
Prithvi is available in such categories of products,
which you can use at the time of 10 lakhs or
above, you can use
hospitalization at maximum 2.5 inches and 2.5 cups, you can make
it optional,
for this you will have to do additional,
after that you can use the ambulance service,
this treatment, which means that if any
treatment is not able to be subscribed,
it is not available in the hospital, then company
treatment, two things are very important in this
that the doctor should have a doctor
and there should be a minimum 3ds treatment  The
prevent
hospitalization is not covered in this, which
HDFC Ergo covers for two minutes
and if there is any subscription of treatment room
rent or any subscription of our channel, then
you must subscribe, if
you can definitely subscribe, you can
subscribe and which
means that if tomorrow
any organ of any policy holder or member gets damaged,
like your liver, kidney or any other organ gets damaged, then the company covers the
policy holder on claim and those who
donate organs are also covered by the company,
in HDFC Ergo it is
covered for half a minute, whereas three to four lakh to four lakh 50 thousand
rupees and five lakh rupees can be subscribed further, that is,
no claim
bonus, now when you click on your policy, then the
company gives you some
no claim bonus, which
in HDFC Ergo different option should have,
for example, if your policy is 10 lakh
and you do not do it for the first year, then
next year it will become 15 lakh, but
you have to keep in mind that as soon as you do it, it happens
like this, this is 10 per cent of
minute and which  That maximum subscription
example if you are a Servi then you can get
maximum up to 15 lakhs by adding no claim bonus in it,
in this the no claim
bonus of Aloe Vera will increase by 50% on Thursday and you will get
Shreya Ghoshal, that is, if you do
not make a claim, you will get 50% option like
Play Karo, here is the giver - to benefit, this can be
used once on Thursday, if
you have a policy of 10 lakhs, if any
subscriber restores it once in the second year, the
best thing in this is that it is
on re-admission basis for the same person, who
cannot avail the Play Store benefit earlier, for example,
if you have to get admitted again, then the
company will make the claim,
in Cheer's recharge option, this is your
recharge once in a year, you can claim
treatment of same person and SIM disease in this, you cannot claim treatment of same person and SIM disease, if
you talk about maternity benefit, then
HD BF Servi  Benefits not
available for the product If your policy is of Rs 50 lakh or
above, then you can get maternity benefit for a
maximum of 2 years.
Ayurvedic treatment subscription is
available. If you subscribe, then you will get
Rs 20,000 if you subscribe. For any existing disease of
yours, treatment is
available after three years in HDFC Ergo. If you
talk about up to date cover in both the companies, then there is no
doubt in anything of HDFC Ergo that if
any policy holder takes it after 1 year, then the
company gives the option to subscribe,
so
subscribe, so that you can get
your cut category 2 by getting many quit treatments done as per your choice
and you
can subscribe. We will
upload the screenshot for you. You can check on the screen
that in this category you will get
pregnancy test against limited tests
set by the company, from which you
can get cashless test done for every family member. We are
uploading the screenshot of that, you
can check. Talking about the width,
in both the companies, this child is covered for up to 1 year.  Servi
102 years while 102 years 3 years
Jhala, if we talk about this account then
in such categories, even the 2 year policy has a
discount of 7.5% and in this also there is the
same 7.5% discount on the 2 year policy
and on the 3 year policy,
subscribe to the flight channel, flight means
calculating the premium of all three policies. If we talk about Servi Panel Hospital, then
ABS Final Year 3000 1000
Hospital Channel Health Insurance
provides a good option which is global
cover. If you subscribe once, then
apart from this, you
can get treatment done in other countries. The
condition in this is such that 10% of the amount will have to be
paid and the benefit should be
in single trap and
hospitalization is not covered in this. There is no
option of global cover available in shares.
We
hope that you have got a lot of clarity from it
and it will
help you a lot in selecting a good insurance product.
Like if you liked the video,
we will share information on it.  If you keep bringing it,
please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for
watching.